Hello.
I'm Kiho Onuma and
Marina Kosaka
Today we are in Shizuoka Prefecture!
Today I'm going to take Marino to my favorite restaurant!
It's my hometown, so I'm going to make Marino fall in love with it!
I'll do my best!
I'm looking forward to it!
Let's go!
We're on the move.
Do you know where we're going? I'm on my way.
A restaurant?
It's a little out of the ordinary.
Really? Marino.
Where is it?
Can I go now?
Where are they going now?
Where do you think?
Fish.
Is it a place where you can eat fish?
Yes.
It starts with a "y.
"A".
Is this the same Mr. Ikesei I mentioned in my essay?
You feel good.
I want to go!
I'm in Thailand now.
I'm doing Thai rice bowls and fried Thai food.
Let's eat Thai!
I want to go to Thailand.
Here I come!
Pie sounds good.
Let's do it now!
Let's do pie. - Let's do pie?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sei-no.
Yuck.
A-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm with you.
Looks so good!
Yay!
It's so beautiful.
Bon appétit!
I'll eat it!
Yum!
Here you go.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
It's so sweet.
Oh, wow.
You can feel how fresh it is.
It's so fresh.
Oh, Ty's happy too.
Hmmm...
Mm-hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
What do you think? Dad's tie.
But it smells like dad.
Smells like my dad?
It's so fresh.
So fresh, so fresh.
So fresh.
Nice and juicy.
Sweet.
Sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet
Sweet, sweet, sweet.
I'll eat it.
Mmm-hmm.
Like big fingers.
Oh, my gosh.
Daddy, I can see too much.
Mmm-hmm.
Puripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripu
Purr purrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!
Purrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!
Puripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripuripu.
Pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre!
I'll give you Pry's rice cakes.
Yeah, I'll do it.
I've got heat on me.
Oh, my God.
Ah!
His mouth is close.
I could eat it.
So fluffy!
Very rag-tag shitai!
Delicious!
Finished!
Thank you for the food!
That was delicious.
How was your father's Thai?
It was so fresh.
I've never had Thai like this before.
I was so impressed.Delicious and impressive!
Delicious today too!
Thank you very much.
Are you full?
I'm full.
Now let's go to a famous cherry blossom viewing spot.
Let's go!
I want to go there!
Wow!
Seino.
Do you want to go to the ball?
Oh!
Ta-da!
Mishima-taisha shrine.
Wow, Mishima's so beautiful.
What did you do?
Health.
You know, health is the most important thing.
And the health of everyone at Buddies.
I made sure to ask for it.
Me too.
May you be happy.
You're so cute!
And all of Spatin.
I wish you all the best.
Ta-da!
Cherry blossoms will be in full bloom from the end of March
Early April is the best time to see the cherry blossoms!
Amazing!
Absolutely beautiful!
There will be an arch of cherry blossoms.
I'm sure it's beautiful.
My eyes darted around a little more.
I'm always so nervous about changing classes in the spring.
I'm so excited.
I've had about six classes since elementary school.
Six?
I've had a lot of days.
From elementary school to high school, there were always a lot of people in my class.
I was so nervous every time I had to change classes.
I got separated from my good friends.
You know what I mean? I'll tell you what.
We didn't switch classes.
Yeah, I know. I heard it was pretty rare.
Have you seen the music video for the third period?
I did.
I watched it so many times.
We'd all get together and...
Dancing in the hallway.
It's amazing.
It's really amazing that they can come in together and dance so well.
When I heard the song for the first time, I thought it was a very nice song.
It's the kind of song that can only be done by the company.
I'm sure it will be a treasured song for the third term students.
I hope so!
I'm back!
I'm going to be in Aichi now.
I'll be appearing on TV and stuff.
I'm heading to Nagoya.
I'll be there.
Bye bye.
I love you so much!
We've arrived in Nagoya!
Good luck tomorrow!
I'll do my best.
I'm now going to appear soon on Tokai Radio's Dai Mai Channel!
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
Yes, I'm Kihoko Onomura and Marina Koga from Sakurazaka 46!
I'm Marina Koga, a member of Sakurazaka 46.
There's a song called "Cool" that's going to be released.
In the song, the word "cool" appears, so please say "cool" with the fans.
I hope fans will join me in saying "cool" in the song.
I think it's going to be a lot of fun.
I performed at the show.
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Yes, we came to Atsuta Horoiken for lunch!
I'll be right back!
Pacar!
Wow!
It's stuffed to the brim!
Bon appétit!
My first HITOMABUKUSHI!
Yup.
It's my first time.
Mmm.
That's great.
I don't know.
It's so crunchy on the outside.
But soft and fluffy on the inside.
It's so delicious.
That's amazing!
I'm telling you, it's amazing.
It's savory.
It's really delicious.
It's really good.
The second step is still to put the noodles in and eat it.
Finished!
Looks delicious!Looks delicious!
Mayonnaise goes well with it.
Oh, my gosh!
A fashionable rabbit.
Oh, man.
Rabbit.
It was an eel!
Now let's get to the third part, the ochazuke!
Wow!
I wonder if it's okay to put it all in.
Looks delicious!
Yum!
Delicious!
It's a nice eel soaked in broth.
It's so good!
More tea goes well with it.
Hey...
The dashi is very effective!
Thank you for the food.
How was it?
It was delicious.
I've never had it before.
I didn't even know how to eat it.
It's so nice that you can eat it in three different ways.
You can change the taste so many times.
It's like a taste of Japan!
I hope you Buddy's will try it too!
I want you all to try it!
Please come!
Here we are in the mountains!
Two days!
It went by so fast, didn't it?
It's not often that I come to the countryside
I don't get to come to the countryside very often.
So we had a lot of fun and did a lot of different things.
And we ate a lot of delicious food!
With Wylan.
It was really fun to be here with Wylan.
It was a great memory.
Thank you so much!